[Music]
do you mind if the Skokie's know your
name would you like to introduce
yourself to the scoby so these are these
are khmer i Scopus I'm here in an Audi
a4 and we're here doing an Audi a4
review review for out EA 4 so this thing
looks like spaceship like howdy did a
great job with the interior in this car
I really like this this whole LCD panel
I think their graphics are tasteful it
feels responsive their interface here is
pretty nice the driver assistance
features on this car leave a lot to be
desired
so here's the cruise control stock and
like you can set it but it's like very
confusing I can pull it in three
directions oh there we go okay I set it
to 60 well I don't think this car has
any sort of adaptive cruise control so I
think if I go here yeah we are just
gaining
it's made to go a little faster
now there's definitely no identities so
yeah if I had continued to let this car
go we would have our crashed into that
minivan so there's this panel that I'm
on here called driver assistance I'm not
really sure what it does but well you
know so the mission of comi I really is
to replace the car interior with a
better one we're letting you buy the
upgrade to a Tesla in your not Tesla car
now unfortunately the scope is asking
any questions
how many scobie's we have 72 oh we got
72 people watching this oh yeah
yeah okay so if this thing has something
called traffic signs I'm gonna show them
this dashboard
it says no traffic sign information
available I see some traffic signs I
don't know why the Mobileye up here this
car does use mobile I believe I believe
this is my q3 this is a 2017 out EA for
what was it driving into this distance
the driver assistance do anything I
don't understand it maybe is this some
setting if the set I'm in a silver car
out EA for if you guys have you Skokie's
one at one at Google these are pretty
nice
this is like very very very tastefully
done look at the Audi logo compared to
the Ford logo that's something you want
in your car this is this is very high
school yeah no no no diesel knows
America oh I see use a lifeline okay
that's kind of what happens if you put
regular gas in it it's not a diesel is
that what this Kofi's are asking oh man
we got we got the this is route 4
yeah route 4 I so you'll check over
there that's hanging sexy new intern
behold it for the day
you guys can rate how well she's doing
stability was no I meant luxury car save
gas Oh could I put regular in here I
don't know I'll have to read my rental
agreement with silver car but yeah so
unfortunately you guys know this is
$10,000 bounty if anybody can get open
pilot running on this car unfortunately
it has flex ray what's exciting about
this car for Karla it just like it looks
like a spaceship man just like look at
this thing right
compare this to like hang on I'm not
answering a comment which one Trenton
what's what are they saying I missed it
if they're saying lewd or vulgar things
you don't have to read that